(Let's get geared up, let's survive, we can still be idiots)
If we all laugh, it'll be all right
Let's ride it out till we burn up Let's get high on one, two, three
Let's make some noise and survive 8, 7, 9
# Can I try Saba?
Can I try Saba?
RAMIREZ: RAMIREZ.
Yes, ma'am.
yeah
check out the instagram link!
Summer of 2020!
Vegetable staple Everland
On my way home from Shin-Yokohama
Pentetsu eating a lunch box from the local Yamaya
No different!
Other just for you!
Matching flowers
It just so happens that we match
Miri Ryoku is amazing!
It's good, isn't it?
It's pretty long.
How is it?
It's warm.
It's hot. He's sleeping.
Look at this.Please see
This beefy day
And here it is
What a surprise!
Familiar to all of you
Familiar
The boy from Shiogama
I'd like to take a look at
What a combination!
It was early in the morning.
The combination is terrible!
Yes, yes, yes...
Tuna?
Tuna and salmon roe bento.
Mosu?
The new one.
I'm pretty sure I've never seen it before.
Summer of Love.
Is it good?
I don't know.
It's so cute.
Bon appétit.
Wow.Wow.
How gorgeous.
Here you go.
Oh.
Yum! Yum!
Delicious.
And...
I bought my first ekiben bento
First Ekiben is gorgeous!
I put a lot of effort into my first ekiben.
That's for sure!
A memorable bento
Delicious!
Seafood, too.
It was delicious.
I'm getting better at this.
I'll go in if I have to.
What?
If we don't get ready soon, we're going down.
Hey, guys.
Hey, girl.
Hey, nyan.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you very much for riding with us.Thank you for riding with us.
We're here.
Laughter.
Good morning.
Good morning, sir.
Did you sleep well?
I'm in a hurry.
What is it?
Seafood.
It's cute.
Look at this.
It's jalapenos, Masaki flavor.
You're buying?
I don't know.
I want to buy one.
I'll buy this one.
Then I'll buy a big one.
You're buying?
Souvenirs for my friends.
It's good.
They're the first to eat two of each.
Why?
Bon appétit.
It's cute.
Oh, he's cute.Oh, you're eating pretty.
What do you think? How do you like it?
It's good.
Is it good?
It tastes like toasted oil.
Oh, my God.
Mmm.
You want some?
I want some.
I love this.
May I? Excuse me. Thank you very much.
Yay!
Crunchy chocolate nut.
Crunchy chocolate nut. What did you order?
What did you say, crunchy sugar?
Crunchy sugar.
Yes!
Ryokko crunchy sugar!
Oh, shimo-shi crunchy sugar!
That's great!
What's that?
Oh, really?
Oh, wow.
Yes, it is.It's true.
Your eyes are hidden.
Yours.
Oh, hey, didn't you have a drink this morning?
What was that? Now?
You didn't have it this morning, did you?
Looks good.
Trompix.
Sky Camera
Camera in the sky.
Yay! Get it!
Yay! Miso katsu miso color with taymesu!
But you know, it's funny because I was only supposed to buy Tames.
I got it!
I was overcome with annoyance.
I'm sorry.
I'm so excited!
That's funny.
So cute!
Hime hime!
Delicious!
Miso Katsu
Delicious.
Amazing.That's awesome.
Cute.
It's big.
Oh, my God.
It's so good!
Yum! Yum!
Delicious!
Let's eat!
What?
Delicious?
Today is the day of Rough Rough's first trip to Nagoya, but I'm traveling separately.
Because I've just participated in the second round of the Under 25 Alley Championship.
I'm going to eat.
This is...
It's sweet asari.
I love asari because of the name, so...
I'm so happy when I eat it.
Please take a look at it.
Please check it carefully.
Please watch your step when you pass by.
It was comfortable.
Thank you for the souvenir.Thank you for the souvenir.
No one will make fun of you if you talk about your dreams. This is where you belong.
I can hear the heartbeat of my chest in motion, the maze of love playing
The photo's today's Romp Rhythm, I'm extraordinaire
I'm an extra, I'm an extra, I'm an extra, I'm an extra, I'm an extra, I'm an extra
I'll destroy everything, and you'll never see me again.
I can't do it, so I can't help it
This is my way of tuning up my mind
From now on, I'm going dark.
I'm going to fall into the darkness of the other world
Sometimes the water is not white
I won't catch any darkness
Miraculous fall into darkness
A retro-sensitive fall into darkness
I have to allow it in my heart
I can't rest
I'll be back soon
Just a little bit more
I'm going to let myself go a little dark.
One more time.
Up, up, up, up.
Rise and shine.Get excited!
Fried bean curd is delicious
Hey, hey, hey!
I love Nagoya!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
I love Aichi
I love Aichi. I love Aichi.
Aichi tail.
That's not even close.
Aichi Aichi Tail.
Everything's different.
Okay, we're here in Nagoya.
I'm here in Nagoya, and I'm in a hurry.
I changed my clothes.
Here's my outfit. Summer.
And I'm off to the venue in Nagoya, where the members are waiting for me.
So, you're going to be performing for about another hour, so please tell us about your enthusiasm.
We have a lot to do in the next 30 minutes, so I'm going to do my best to keep the excitement going until the end.
We're going to play a lot of songs, and this time we're going to play a big song.
I hope everyone will get excited!
How are you doing before the live?
I'm not sure if my voice will work.
Is it said that you have a sweet voice?
I don't shank.I'm not sulking.
I'll do my best.
Harurun is good at it and always pulls me along.
I'll do my best so that I can do my best even if you can't speak.
I'll do my best, everyone.
Make it last! Make it last!
Fan content on the Internet!
Transformation! Face! Passion! Happiness! Smile! Growth! Confidence! Gratitude! Charm!
We, LaRuff~!
Let's go for it!
♪ Bangkok Ten, Bangkok Ten already, 'cause I love you
I'll sing it for you
Ten billion points, more empty hands
If you're celebrating, that's all that matters.
If you sing, you're a cute carnival idol
Now's the time to make love half a girl
I'll make you the highest, the furthest, the hottest
Hallelujah
Here's where we start, right in front of you
Even on the darkest of days I'll say my name to the wind Smile, smile, smile
Good Christmas Cappy Christmas Smile
GO!
To the tears of a bird
Now it's not a waste of timeNow, it's not a waste of time.
I finally got to the page.
Give it back at the end.
Thank you my friend
I'll sing you a sparkling song
I chewed it all back then
The heartbreak that was stopped
It makes me sick inside
For the sake of happiness
If tears fall
Someday a little flower will bloom
Just like that
I'll see eternity once more
I'll see
I still don't have a lover
The Emperor is alive, the Emperor is here, and the Emperor is happy signing for the Emperor.
Click, click, click.
I've dreamed of being an idol since I was a child
I won't give up now, I won't go completely
Maybe only be strong, I can't build up my self-confidence
To achieve my dream Hi! Hi!
We're perfect!
Hip-jumping with gratitude
It's exciting on both of our parts.
But, right?But, right?
The best! Strongest!
Yes! Thanks!
To sadness
Laughter
Love to remember
No! No!
Keep thinking that
I'll go on to the next
You can make it!
Let's get it
The map of your dreams
I don't care if someone cries and has fun
I won't let it be a dream
No one will make fun of you
They won't make fun of me
It's not even terribly bad
I just wanted to say something.
I don't want to.
I don't think about it
Peace and quiet.
Erlulu, kitty, kitty, kitty.
Kindness in Office Life Instant Guitar
Gentleness, office life, instant guitar.
Hurt people, a lot of tears, not in vainHurt people, a lot of tears, not in vain
I'll never give up, I'll never give up, I'll never give up, I'll never give up, I'll never give up.
I can't stop, I can't stop, I can't stop, I can't stop, I can't stop.
I've been living my life till I turn it into my own
Smile, smile, smile, smile
You're the youth of my life
You're beautiful
I've been sad for a long time, starting with you
I don't need words
But I still have to let go of my feelings
I'll forget the pain and walk
I'll never get tired. I'm going home.
Bye bye Nagoya
Oops, I'm awake.
Bon appétit!
Bon appétit.
How's it going? I think you're right.
It's good.
Does it melt?
That's how I feel.
Here's how I feel about it.
You want some? No?
Do you want to give it to me? Yes?
Cute.cunning
cunning
cunningcunning
Mocking
My Hikaru
If you're a fan, you've been an idol geek for a long time.
Shots and sotto voce idols aren't good enough for them anymore.
Wow!
Just one!
I really want one!
Just one person, and I'll definitely get more of my guesses.
I can get two shots now!
Aah!
I said this in my idol persona.
Thank you for watching to the end!
I'll be winking at you today!
I'm looking forward to working with you.